I want to switch from test e to test
indan weight I hope the longer eser will
allow me to aromatize less and to have
more stable blood levels I plan to do
one injection per week instead of the
three I do currently on test e what are
your thoughts about
that the longer eser of testosterone I
think uh on deonate is anywhere from 14
to 21 days I believe it's 21 days I'm
not a fan of long Esters they take five
half lives uh just like any other
medication to reach a steady state they
take five Half Lives to clear if you
don't like the way they're working uh
the ability to control and manage how
shbg binds to the hormone and how much
of it is released is now diminished
because you're no longer utilizing a
Esther that allows you to make
adjustments on the fly in a relatively
short period of time so I believe this
gentleman is probably in Europe or
outside of the United States because
neither Esther is popular here medically
we use testost cenate primarily and Nate
is available on deonate is not uh but I
would encourage him if he is overseas
and he does not have access to cypionate
and anate is the next best Ester that I
would choose so I would stay with what
he's on but I would have it managed by a
provider who fully understands how to
treat men and their sex hormones
correctly